Okay, so there are two ways to accept a
GitHub collaboration request. The first
one is definitely the easiest
and that is you'll get an email. You can
click view invitation and then you can
walk through the prompts to accept it
from there. Um I'm going to show you the
way to do it through GitHub. Um this one
is a bit of a runaround. Sorry, I moved
my picture. Okay. So, what you're going
to do is you're going to log in to the
account that got the request to
collaborate. You're going to click on
your profile picture and you're going to
go to organizations
and there at the top you can see demo
repo invitation expires in 7 days. So,
maybe not the easiest thing in the world
to find, but then you can go ahead and
click on that repo and it'll take you
there and you can see what's in the repo
so that you know what you're accepting
before you accept it. Um, and right here
there's a banner that says we've been
invited to collaborate. So, we're going
to view the invitation. And if you were
coming from your email, you'll be taken
to this page. Or if you um were coming
the other direction that I just showed
you, you'll be taken to this page. And
you can click click accept invite. And
now we can see and we can make changes
to this repository. So, if you've made
it to this point, uh you'll get this
banner up at the top that says you now
have push access to teaches tech demo
repo repository and or whichever
repository you just got access to and
you can now successfully collaborate on
GitHub.